In Catalan.cpp
This file compiles and runs accurately on my Mac terminal. It takes in command line input from the 
terminal. 

GreedyRobot
I took the variable name as xR and yR to represent the x and y coordinates that the robot is at. 
I took the variable name as xT and yT to represent the x and y coordinates that the treasure is at.
The reason I chose these names is because it was given in the directions that the robot is at (xr, yr) and the treasure is at (xt,yt). 
